# **Dennis** Campoverde-Lema

Web Developer



## **Personal Info**

**Address** 

2100 Dickens In Saint Paul, MN 55112

**Phone** 

6129102245

E-mail

dennyslema441@gmail.com

Date of birth

1995-04-08

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dennis\_ca mpoverde-lema

## Skills

Client Relations

I dealt with temper and calmed clients

Adept

I can handle any situation with any pressure

Bilingual

I can understand and read in Spanish

Java Script

I know the basic but will master if needed for this company I have recently started a program that is sponsor by the University of Minnesota for web development. I have done many things with Java, HTML, CSS, jQuery, JSON, Bootstraps, and firebase date. i have worked in the service industry for 7 years. I have many experience with dealing and handling with "good" and "bad' guest. I been the first person to get called upon when a guest is having a bad time or is not making their concern clear. My passion is to learn different ways into improving myself to help the company i work for better. I am extremely hard worker. I will try my best into solving problems and finding solutions.

## **Experience**

Front server attendant 2011-08 -

present Kelber catering

- Train new employees into company procedures
- Lead small teams to finish task set by supervisor
- I been the "go to guy" for small task that required small details

**Hyatt regency** 2016-02 present

Banquet server

- I have assemble and manage small functions on my own
- Discuss with clients with any schedule changes
- Set and input procedures for new hires

## **Education**

present

**Cristo Rey Jesuit Highschool** 2010-08 -

2014-06 I was part a STEM program sponsor by the University of Minnesota. I did

robotics and was a part of SHPE (Society of Hispanic Professional Engineers)

Minneapolis community and technical college 2014-08 -

2015-01 Did mathematics for a year and a half but took a break

**University of Minnesota Boot camp** 2019-01 -

> I am have started a program that is sponsor by the university of Minnesota and i have learn many new skills that will allow me to do my job as efficiently as

possible for the company

#### CSS

I have a firm grip on what is need from this program

HTML

I can set up divs, ID, and classes

jQuery

Like java i know the basic but will be eager to learn more

JSON

I recently learned this and will get better in time with this